Stephanie Fajardo

WEB DEVELOPER AND DESIGNER

404-907-3848

sfajardo7@gatech.edu



Atlanta, GA

in

linkedin.com/in/stephfajardo

github.com/stephtf

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

My greatest strengths include my ability to problem solve, think creatively, and maintain a high level of self-motivation. I offer a diverse skillset as someone who is trained in full-stack web development, UX design, qualitative research, and education. I excel at organizing and completing large projects, meeting tight deadlines, and working cooperatively with others in teams.

EDUCATION

GEORGIA TECH FULL STACK CODING BOOTCAMP

3/9/2022

GOOGLE UX CERTIFICATE

11/19/2021

PHD, HISTORY

University of Michigan 08/21/2020

MA, TEACHING

University of Washington 12/16/2011

BA, HISTORY BA, ANTHROPOLOGY BA, SPANISH

University of Washington 6/11/2010

TOOLS

Figma
Adobe XD
Word
Excel
Powerpoint

LANGUAGES

English (native)
Spanish (proficient)
Tagalog (proficient)
French (beginner)

WORK EXPERIENCE

POSTDOCTORAL FELLOW

Georgia Institute of Technology / Atlanta, GA / August 2021 - Present

- Assembled Twitter API to analyze audience reception of 90 Day Fiancé
- Organized and examined archival sources related to US military families in the Philippines
- Developed an undergraduate course on US gender history

POSTDOCTORAL FELLOW

University of Michigan / Ann Arbor, MI / August 2020 - August 2021

- Planned a transnational panel on anti-Asian violence, bringing together scholars and activists from the US and Australia
- Wrote and presented a research paper on gender and anti-Asian violence
- Published three articles for SAGE Filipinx Studies Encyclopedia and a book review for the Journal of Asian Studies

RESEARCH SUPERVISOR

Bentley Historical Library / Ann Arbor, MI / May 2019 - August 2020

- Managed a large archival research project on the topic of US colonialism in the Philippines
- Facilitated research and digital skills workshops for undergraduates
- Oversaw the creation of an open-access, digital exhibit of archival findings

RESEARCH FELLOW AND LECTURER

University of Michigan / Ann Arbor, MI / August 2018 - May 2019

- Conducted oral interviews with subjects in Tagalog for a project on gender and US military history in the Philippines
- Designed and taught History 195, an introductory historical writing course
- Delivered lectures and led students in large-group discussion

SKILLS

CODING	UX DESIGN	RESEARCH
HTML	User Research	Qualitative Methods
CSS	Wireframing	Interviewing
javascript	Prototyping	Data Management
node.js	Usability Studies	Affinity Mapping
express	Universal Design	Critical Analysis

OTHER SKILLS Git / version con

Git/version control Testing/debugging Responsive design 120wpm typing speed Video editing